theinfiniteactuary.com 2019-05-30

# Privacy Policy - The Infinite Actuary

### Privacy Statement

The Infinite Actuary, hereon referred to as "TIA", is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you an excellent and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to TIA's website and governs data collection and usage. By using TIA's website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. 

### Collection of your Personal Information

TIA collects personally identifiable information, such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card information. TIA may also collect information about your computer. This information can include your IP address, Operating System, browser type, referring website addresses, domain names, access times, files downloaded and videos viewed. This information is for system administration and in order to create reports. Statistical data shared with trusted third parties about our users' browsing actions and patterns does not identify any individual. TIA collect information when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, or use our online seminar/education tools. 

### Use of your Personal Information

The information collected from you is used to personalize user's experience, to improve the website, to improve customer service, to administer contests/promotions/surveys or other site features, to process transactions and to send periodic emails. 

TIA does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. TIA may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to TIA, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. 

TIA may also keep track of which pages our users and guests visit with TIA's website, in order to determine which of our products and services are most popular. TIA may also track your progress through our online seminars/education tools and ratings of lessons to compile your data with other users to anonymously share general statistics with other TIA instructors and users. 

TIA will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on TIA or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of TIA; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of TIA, or the public. 

### Protection of your Personal Information

TIA secures your information using an SSL certificate when a user places an order or enters/submits/accesses their personal information. TIA use a payment gateway provider and do not store your credit card information on our servers. All the personal identifiable information you provide TIA are stored on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. 

### Use of Cookies

TIA uses "cookies" to help remember and process the items in the shopping cart, personalize your online experience and compile aggregate data about site traffic and interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. TIA may also use trusted third party services, including Google Analytics, that track this information on our behalf. Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track visitor interactions as in our case, where they are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. TIA then use the information to compile reports and to help us improve our site. 

Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. These cookies are used to store information, such as the time that the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before and what site referred the visitor to the web page. 

Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit our site - for more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, visit this Google page: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

### California Online Privacy Protection Act

According to CalOPPA TIA agrees to the following: 

  * Users can visit our site anonymously 
  * Once this privacy policy is created, TIA will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website. 
  * Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above. 

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes: 

  * On our Privacy Policy Page 

Users are able to change their personal information: 

  * By logging in to their account 

How does our site handle do not track signals? 

  * TIA honor them and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. 

Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking? 

  * TIA do allow 

### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

TIA does not specifically market children under 13 

### Fair Information Practices

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices TIA will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur: 

TIA will notify the users via email 

  * Within 7 business days 

TIA will notify the users via in site notification 

  * Within 7 business days 

TIA agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors 

### CAN SPAM Act

TIA collect your email address: 

To send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. 

To process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders 

  * TIA may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service. 

To market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to your clients after the original transaction has occured 

To be accordance with CANSPAM TIA agrees to the following: 

  * TIA will NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses 
  * TIA will identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way 
  * TIA will include the physical address of our business or site headquarters 
  * TIA will monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used. 
  * TIA will honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly 
  * TIA will give an 'opt-out' or 'unsubscribe' option 

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can 

  * Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email. 

### Contact Information

The Infinite Actuary, LLC 

www.theinfiniteactuary.com 

3590-B Hwy 31 South Ste. #227 

Pelham, AL 35124 

United States of America 

customerservice@theinfiniteactuary.com 

888-842-1006 

Updated 8/12/2014
